in this tutorial we'll be going over how
在本教程中，我们将介绍如何
you can create half tone gradients using
您可以使用以下工具创建半色调渐变
inkscape so to get started the first
所以Inkscape是第一个入门的
thing I'm going to do is create a new
我要做的是创建一个新的
document size to 1280x720 your document
文档大小调整为1280x720您的文档
doesn't have to be that size just make
不一定非得有那么大的尺寸
your document in whatever size you'd
无论您想要什么大小的文档
like your gradient to be
就像你的渐变
so I'll turn on snapping up here and
所以我会在这里打开抓拍
I'll grab my rectangle tool and I'm
我拿起我的矩形工具，然后我
going to snap to the corners of my
我要抓住我的眼角
document and click and drag to create a
文档，然后单击并拖动以创建
rectangle in the size of my document
我的文档大小为矩形
now I'm going to make this rectangle
现在我要把这个长方形
white and I'm going to apply a black and
白色和我要涂上黑色和
white gradient so let me open up the
白色渐变所以让我打开
fill and stroke menu by coming up here
通过进入此处来填充和描边菜单
to where it says object and selecting
到它显示对象的位置，并选择
fill and stroke
填充和描边
now Under The Fill tab I'm going to
现在在填充选项卡下，我将执行以下操作
select this button right here that says
选择这里的按钮，上面写着
linear gradient
线性梯度
and when we get these handles here on
当我们把这些把手放在这里时
the screen I'm going to select this
屏幕我要选择这个
handle over here on the right and I'm
把手放在右边，我就是
going to make this one black
我要把这件弄成黑色
and then I'm going to take this gradient
然后我要用这个梯度
handle and snap it to the bottom right
握住它并将其按到右下角
corner and I'll take this gradient
拐角处，我要这个渐变
handle and snap it to the top right
握住它并将其卡在右上角
corner
拐角
and now we have a white to black radiant
现在我们有了从白到黑的光芒
like that
就像这样
so now let's open up the layers menu let
那么现在让我们打开Layers菜单
me grab my select tool let's come up
我拿起我的选择工具，让我们上来吧
here to where it says layer and select
此处显示Layer并选择
layers and objects
层和对象
and what we're going to do now is we're
我们现在要做的是
going to turn off actually no we're
我要关掉了，不，我们要
going to lock the layer here and then
要在这里锁定图层，然后
click the plus icon over here to create
单击此处的加号图标以创建
a new layer
一个新的层
I'm going to click add I'm going to
我要单击添加，我要
leave the default as it is make sure
保留缺省值不变，确保
it's above current and click add and now
它位于当前上方，然后单击添加并立即
I'm going to zoom in on the top left
我要放大左上角
corner of my document over here and I'm
我文件的一角在这里，我是
going to grab my ellipse tool I'm going
去拿我的椭圆工具，我要去
to snap to the top left corner and I'm
捕捉到左上角，我是
going to click and drag to create a
要单击并拖动以创建
circle and I'm going to hold to the
圆圈，我要坚持住
control key to make sure we're creating
Ctrl键以确保我们正在创建
a perfectly round circle and I'll make
一个完美的圆圈，我会做一个
it about that size right there don't
它就在那里那么大，不会
worry too much about the size at this
太担心这个的大小了
point we can go back and change that
我们可以回到过去，改变这一点
later
后来
now this step is important if you're
现在这一步很重要，如果你是
using one of the newer versions of
使用较新版本的
inkscape because I noticed by default it
Inkscape，因为我默认注意到它
sets the stroke to unknown so come over
将笔划设置为未知，请过来
here to the fill and stroke Tab and
此处到填充和描边选项卡，然后
under the stroke paint tab if you have
在笔划绘制选项卡下，如果您有
this question mark box highlighted just
这个问号框刚刚突出显示
click this x right here to make sure
单击此处的x以确保
there's no stroke because if that is
没有中风，因为如果这是
enabled then it's going to mess up what
使能，那么它将会搞砸什么？
we're about to do
我们接下来要做的是
so now once you've done that
所以，一旦你做到了这一点
grab your selection tool with the object
抓起带有对象的选择工具
selected go to edit
所选转到编辑
clone create titled clones
克隆创建有标题的克隆
and the settings we're going to use here
以及我们将在此处使用的设置
we're going to use Trace
我们将使用跟踪
select the option right here that says
选择此处的选项，该选项显示
trace the drawing under the Clones we
在我们的克隆体下追踪图形
want to trace by color
想按颜色描画吗？
we're going to leave these set to zero
我们将把这些设置为零
and the only two options we want enabled
我们希望启用的只有两个选项
over here are size and color and then
这里有尺寸和颜色，然后
come down here and choose width and
到这里来，选择宽度和
height over rows and columns now where
行和列的高度现在在哪里
it says width and height input the width
它说宽度和高度输入宽度
and height of your document my document
文档的高度和高度My Document
was 1280x720 so I have that there
是1280x720，所以我有这个
already and then I just have this
已经有了，然后我就有了这个
enabled here to save these settings next
在此处启用以下一步保存这些设置
time I use this so I'll click create now
现在我要使用它，所以我将点击Create Now
and once you do that you can see it
一旦你这样做了，你就可以看到它
generates those it generates that black
产生那些它产生的黑色
circle over the linear gradient and
线性渐变上的圆圈和
turns it into this halftone gradient so
将其转换为半色调渐变
let's work with this some more let's
让我们继续努力，让我们再来一次
first go back to our layers menu let me
首先回到我们的层菜单，让我
collapse this and I'll turn off the
把这个折叠起来，我就会关掉
visibility of layer 1. so now we just
第一层的可见性。所以现在我们只需要
have the halftone gradient and if you
有半色调渐变，如果你
want to change the size of these dots
想要更改这些点的大小
you could zoom in on this let me grab
你可以放大这个让我抓取
the original dot over here
原来的圆点在这里
and let me turn off snapping now because
现在让我关闭捕捉功能，因为
that'll just get in the way and I'll
这只会妨碍我，我会
make this a little smaller
把这个做小一点
and you can see what happens as I make
你可以看到当我做了什么
that smaller it makes the gradient
它使坡度变得更小
smaller as well and I can make this
也要小一点，我可以做这个
bigger and get the opposite effect
变得更大并得到相反的效果
now we have that effect right there and
现在我们就在那里产生了这种效果，
anything I do to this object will also
我对此对象所做的任何操作也将
be applied to the rest of these dots so
应用于这些点的其余部分，因此
you can change the color now if you'd
如果你愿意，你现在可以换颜色了
like as well
喜欢也一样
and there you go that is how you can
就这样，这就是你可以
create a simple halftone gradient using
创建一个简单的半色调渐变使用
inkscape if you found this lesson useful
Inkscape如果你觉得这一课有用
then consider checking out my inkscape
那就考虑看看我的Inkscape吧
master class it's a collection of over
大师类，它是一个集合
60 videos where I go over all of the
60个视频，我浏览了所有
tools and features in inkscape and I
Inkscape和I中的工具和功能
explain what they are and demonstrate
解释它们是什么并演示它们
how they work kind of like how I did in
它们的工作原理有点像我在
this video we even have a private
这个视频我们甚至有一个私人的
Community where you can ask questions
您可以提出问题的社区
and get help from me anytime you want
只要你愿意，随时向我寻求帮助
and best of all there's no monthly
最棒的是没有月刊
membership fees you just pay 17 one time
会员费你只需一次性付17英镑
and you're in for Life I'll have some
你要终身监禁，我要喝一些
information about that down below if you
下面是关于这方面的信息，如果你
want to check that out as always thanks
我想一如既往地检查一下，谢谢
for watching
观看
[Music]
[音乐]
thank you
谢谢